Here's your order,
bro. You're a student.
Oh, yes, he's working so hard. He's
studying and even working a part-time job
.  Everyone takes orders and
fills their stomachs, but
no one even asks if he has eaten or not.
At least he feels happy when I ask him
.  Bro, have you eaten?
How do you look? Come on, why should I
eat from your order? Oh,
I didn't ask that. Bro, it's getting late, have you
eaten or not? I asked in general. If you
don't believe me, open your order and
check. I will
resign from my position because the food quantity has decreased a little.
Bro, you are misunderstanding me.
My mind is very good.   Don't keep your
mouth shut, I'll go if your doubts are cleared.
Sir, the days are not good, go carefully.
Any day, he will understand my goodness,
realize his mistake, kneel at my
feet and ask for forgiveness.  Are
you warning me, my son?